Following this video, you will get
完成这节视频后 你将练习
some practice with much of what we have done in this lesson.
我们这节课中学习的大量内容
But in this video, we are going to cover how to
不过这节视频中我们将要学习如何
make a quick train to split using scikit-learn.
使用 scikit-learn 快速训练拆分
Here, you can see the documentation for creating
这里你可以发现使用 scikit-learn
a training and testing dataset using scikit-learn.
创建一个训练和测试数据集的文档
In this video, we will be doing just a single train test split.
这节视频中我们只进行单个训练测试的拆分
But often in practice,
不过一般在实际中
you'll do a train test split and then you will perform cross validation
你会训练测试切分 然后对训练数据
on the training data and you will use the test data as a final test.
进行交叉验证 然后使用测试数据作为最终测试
The documentation is provided below for your reference as well.
下面提供的文档也可以作为参考
First, let's split our data into training and testing data.
首先我们拆分数据 训练和测试数据
Okay, so here's our data and the necessary libraries.
好 这是我们的数据和必要的库
Let's create a train test split.
我们来创建训练测试的拆分
And essentially, what this should take is,
基本上来说 具体步骤是这样的
if we look at the docs,
如果我们查看文档
see down here, it should take an X and a Y.
看到下面这里 应该利用一个 X 和一个 Y
So, it takes your X and your Y.
那么这里使用你的 X 和 Y
It takes the test size value so,
也使用测试规模值
this is a percentage of your data that you want to be in
这是在测试集里你想得到的数据百分比
the test set and then it takes a random state.
然后这是随机状态
And that's just so that the random split that you
而且你得到的随机拆分
get is something that you can make sure other people can get,
是可以确保其他人也能得到
if that's what you are trying to do.
如果你希望这样做
And we should create those X's and Y's,
我们应该创建这些 X 和 Y
so I'm just going to say X equals df and it basically
我会将 X 表示为默认值
equals everything that's not the price and I don't actually care about that house ID,
相当于不是价格的任何东西 这里不考虑房屋编号
so I'm going to leave it out as well.
所以也删除了房屋编号
Great, now you can see we have a training response and a testing response.
好 现在你可以发现我们得到训练反应和测试反应
So the training response and a testing response.
对于训练反应和测试反应
As well as a training set of
以及解释特征的训练集
explanatory features and a testing set of explanatory features.
和解释特征的测试集
This is something you should do right away.
这也是你应该立即做的事情
Oftentimes people will do this after they do feature engineering,
通常人们会在完成特征工程后这样做
like you saw in an earlier concept,
在之前的概念中你已经见到过
like subtracting the mean and dividing by the standard deviation before splitting.
例如拆分前减去平均数和除以标准差
But this is cheating,
但是这具有欺骗性
because using that information from the test set,
因为使用测试集的信息
is using something that you don't actually have in your training set.
是使用训练集中不包含的内容
Great, if you take the mean of your data before you split it,
好 在拆分前你得到数据的平均数
then that mean is based on information on
这意味着基于测试集的信息
the test set that you shouldn't actually have in your training data.
训练数据中实际上不包含测试集
Now, we're going to try fitting a few linear models to this data set.
现在我们想要拟合这个数据集的线性模型
We'll be using scikit-learn,
使用 scikit-learn
which is going to be a little bit different than what you
这与你之前使用 statsmodels 时
saw in the previous parts using stat's models.
见到的有些不同
We end up at the docs and you can see we can import it like this.
我们最后得到文档 你可以看到我们这样导入它
Here, we can specify that we want a true intercept and actually that's the default.
这里可以说明我们想要一个正确的截距 实际上是默认值
So, we don't have to give it that intercept that we've been doing in the previous parts.
那么我们不能使用之前部分曾经使用的截距
And you'll notice that they use the pre-processing,
你会注意到它们使用预处理
like we saw in the previous part, in this normalize,
与我们在之前见到的一样 在这个标准化中
if we specify this is true,
如果我们指定为真
by default it doesn't do that but that gets
默认情况下不能这样做
away from having to pre-process your data ahead of time.
这样无法提前预处理你的数据
And then, there are these parts down here.
然后下面这是这些部分
In general, what we do is we instantiate our linear regression model first.
一般来说我们首先要用具体例证说明线性回归
So, I'm just going to call this lm.
那么我把它命名为 lm
Okay, so I'll use all the defaults.
好 我使用所有默认值
I'll just use whatever the default values are.
无论默认值是什么 我只使用默认值
So, we instantiate it and then we fit it and if we go back and look at the docs,
我们用具体例证进行说明 然后拟合模型 如果回去查看文档
you can see using the fit,
你会注意到利用拟合
we should pass in the X and then the Y.
我们应该传递到 X 然后是 Y 中
And in general, we fit our model based on the training data.
我们通常根据训练数据拟合模型
And then that's something that's actually going to be stored within the lm function.
然后这是最终存储在 lm 函数中的内容
So, if you're comfortable with object oriented programming,
如果你熟练使用以对象为中心的编程
basically this is stored as attribute information within lm.
这基本上可以在 lm 中存储为属性信息
And then usually, what we do is we predict and then we score.
然后我们进行预测并打分
So, the prediction is something where we predict only on the test data and then we score
这样我们只是根据测试数据得到预测 然后
on how well our test predictions match our actual test values.
我们对测试预测值和实际测试值的匹配度进行打分
We instantiate, we fit,
用具体例证说明 拟合
we predict, and then we score.
预测 然后打分
And actually, we usually predict on
实际上我们一般根据测试集进行预测
the test set and then we'll score on our task set as well.
然后也对任务集进行打分
We can also just use the default,
我们也可以只使用默认值
so the default score here is an R-squared value.
这里默认分数是 R 平方值
So, we can see how well it does.
那么我们可以看到效果怎么样
And you'll notice if we use the built in,
你会注意到如果我们使用嵌入
it just takes the X and the Y.
利用 X 和 Y
And so we don't actually have to do this,
实际上我们不需要这样做
if we're not using one of the other ones,
如果没有使用其中的 1
which it just depends on what you want.
这取决于你想得到的结果
Like if you don't want an R-squared value,
例如如果你不想得到 R 平方值
the way that we're going to do it here doesn't work.
我们这里做的就没有效果
Right. So, it knows what the model is once it's fit and then basically it uses
好 这里我们知道了模型如何拟合 然后基本上
this X test data and this Y test data
使用这个 X 测试数据和 Y 测试数据
along with what it would predict from the model here and it gives you a score back.
以及从这个模型中预测的内容和返回的分数
So, you still have to build your dummy variables, right.
这样你仍然需要创建自己的虚拟变量
So, we just tried to pass all of these things in,
我们只想传递所有内容
so you could just pass in the dummy variables.
这里你可以只传递虚拟变量
But let's make this simple.
我们可以更加简化
We'll get rid of style and we'll get rid of the neighborhood.
删除风格和街区
And we'll just pass the area here.
我们这里只传递面积这一变量
Great, and you can see that our score on
好 你会看到我们测试数据的分数
the test data is approximately 68 percent using the area,
约为 68% 利用面积
the bedrooms, and the bathrooms.
卧室和卫生间
In general, using your score from the test data
一般来说 我们更倾向于使用测试数据的分数
is much preferred to just using the score from a training dataset.
而不是只使用训练数据集中的分数
It shows how well your model performs on new data it hasn't seen.
它体现了你的模型如何完成没遇到过的新数据
This is something that we could do by changing these variables here and seeing
我们通过改变这些变量 观察
which models perform best on the test data
哪些模型能够最好地完成测试数据
and then using that model in practice moving forward.
然后在练习中使用这个模型继续进行